{
    "subject": "resource/Groningen_Europapark_railway_station",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Groningen Europapark",
    "human_readable": "The name of Groningen Europapark railway station is Groningen Europapark.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9853776693344116,
            "question": "What is the name of Groningen Europapark railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9845855832099915,
            "question": "Is there another name for Groningen Europapark railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9801617860794067,
            "question": "Is Groningen Europapark a railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8849315047264099,
            "question": "Where is Groningen Europapark located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8637422919273376,
            "question": "What is the history of Groningen Europapark railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8313236236572266,
            "question": "Is Groningen Europapark a popular destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8181509375572205,
            "question": "What kind of transportation connects to Groningen Europapark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7854654788970947,
            "question": "What services are offered at Groningen Europapark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6627306938171387,
            "question": "Does Groningen Europapark have a specific type of building?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5963114500045776,
            "question": "Can people travel to other cities from Groningen Europapark?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Groningen Europapark railway station is Groningen Europapark.",
            "html": "dbpedia_941_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Groningen Europapark have a specific type of building?",
            "html": "dbpedia_941_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What services are offered at Groningen Europapark?",
            "html": "dbpedia_941_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of transportation connects to Groningen Europapark?",
            "html": "dbpedia_941_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_941_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis triple is correct according to the documents. The documents provide information about the name, location, and other details of the Groningen Europapark railway station, confirming that its name is indeed Groningen Europapark."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Groningen Europapark is an unstaffed railway station in Groningen, the Netherlands,\" which supports the statement that the name of the railway station is Groningen Europapark."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}